Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Board of Governors fonds
1963 - 2009
F-33
20.66 m of textual records and other material
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Board of Governors
The Board of Governors is the University's primary governing body. As established by the Universities Act of 1963, the Board originally consisted of eleven members: the Chancellor, President, three members elected by the Senate, and six others who were appointed by the Lieutenant-Governor in Council. The Universities Act of 1974 increased the number of board members to fifteen (its current number). The Board now includes eight government appointees (two of whom are nominated by the Alumni Association), two elected faculty members, two elected students, 1 elected staff member, and the Chancellor and the President who serve as ex officio members.
The Board of Governors is responsible for the management, administration and control of property, revenue, business and affairs of the University. With the approval of the University Senate, the Board establishes procedures for the selection of candidates for President, deans, Librarian, Registrar, and other senior academic administrators as the Board may designate. The Board also appoints these officials as well as professors and other members of the teaching staff. The Board has the power to fix salaries and define the duties and tenure of office for its appointees, but members of the teaching staff may not be appointed, promoted or removed except upon the recommendation of the President. The Board receives from the President and analyses or adopts with or without modifications the budgets for operating and capital expenditures; fixes the fees to be paid by students; administers funds, grants, fees, endowments and other assets; and, with the approval of Senate, has the power to determine the number of students that may be accommodated at the University.
Chairs of the Board:
Gordon M. Shrum (1963-1968)
Richard E. Lester (1968-1971)
Kenneth P. Caple (1972)
Paul T. Cote (1972-1976, 1981-1982)
Ray Parkinson (1976-1981)
Fred H. Moonen (1982-1987, 1990-1994)
Donald J. Hudson (1988-1990)
Yvonne Cocke (1994-1996)
Tazeen Nathoo (1996-1997)
David Bond (1997-1998)
Jack Kowarsky (1998-1999)
Evaleen Jaager Roy (1999-2002)
Brandt C. Louie (2002-2005)
published
Full
Revised
Title based on the name of the creating body.
Includes 2 sound recordings, 2 CD-ROMs, 1 floppy disk, and 1 enamel pin.
Sound recordings are located in series 6 and 8 and include 14 audio reels (originals), 18 audio cassettes (access copies), and 1 audio cassette (original). CD-ROMs are located in series 11 as well as series 8, sub-series 20. The floppy disk is located in series 8, sub-series 1. The enamel pin is located in series 8, sub-series 20.
The fonds consists of records arising from the mandated functions of the Board of Governors as described in the administrative history. The fonds includes meeting minutes, agendas, and supporting documents; reports; financial papers; contracts; architectural drawings; search and review committee records including c.v.'s, reference letters, and appointment forms; news clippings and other documents. The fonds also includes a collection of policies and procedures, many of which had to be approved by the Board.
The fonds is arranged into the following series:
- [Official Minutes](f-33-1)
- [Agenda support papers](f-33-2)
- [Policies and procedures](f-33-3)
- [Correspondence](f-33-4)
- [Board reports](f-33-5)
- [Special hearings](f-33-6)
- [Committees](f-33-8)
- [Minute appendices and indexes](f-33-9)
- [Meeting dockets](f-33-10)
- [Board Retreats and Strategy Sessions](f-33-11)
Researchers should note that there are two series with overlapping contents. The contents of these two series (F-33-1 and F-33-2) is similar but not identical.
Researchers should also note that there is no series 7. Series 7 (Presidential committees) was retired August 2023 and the records were arranged as sub-sub-series [1968-1979 Presidential Search Committees](f-33-8-1-1), under sub-series [Presidential Search and Review Committees](f-33-8-1).
Kowarsky, Jack; Bond, David; Nathoo, Tazeem; Cocke, Yvonne; Hudson, Donald J.; Parkinson, Ray; Shrum, Gordon; Lester, Richard E.; Caple, Kenneth P.; Moonen, Fred H.; Coté, Paul T.; Roy, Evaleen Jaager; Sound recordings; Textual records; Multi-media
Further accruals are expected.
Records are subject to British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA). Access restrictions may apply to records containing personal information or confidential information (e.g. legal advice). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release. See the file lists and consult the reference archivist for more information.
A file list is available.
- Official Minutes, 1963 - 2006; F-33-1; 1.05 m of textual records
  published
  Series comprises official minutes of regular meetings including open, closed and confidential sessions as well as official minutes of special Board meetings. Includes official appendices comprising committee minutes, correspondence, financial statements, correspondence, reports, lists of appointments and other documents. Open sessions are open to all members of the University community and the public; closed sessions are restricted to Board members, the Board secretary, the Vice-Presidents' group, the director of Media and Public Relations, and anyone else who has the permission of the Board Chair to attend. Confidential sessions are restricted to Board members, the Secretary of the Board, and anyone else who has the permission of the Board Chair to attend. These records are used to document all deliberations of the Board including the passage of motions and resolutions and the approval of governing decisions. Until approximately 1975, all Board sessions were considered closed. After that time, meetings were divided into open and closed sessions. In 2004, official meeting minutes began to be filed together with agenda support papers into docket packages. To view official meeting minutes from 2004 onwards, see series F-33-10 Meeting dockets.
  Records are subject to British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA). See the note on *Restrictions on access* in the [fonds-level description](f-33) for more information.
  - Official minutes Vol. 1 1/2, 1963 - 1964; F-33-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Official minutes Vol. 1 2/2, 1963 - 1964; F-33-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 2 1/3, 1965; F-33-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 2 2/3, 1965; F-33-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 2 3/3, 1965; F-33-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 3 1/2, 1966; F-33-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 3 2/2, 1966; F-33-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 3a, 1966; F-33-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-1)
  - Official minutes Vol. 4, 1967; F-33-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 4a, 1967; F-33-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 5 1/2, 1968; F-33-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 5 2/2, 1968; F-33-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 6 1/2, 1969; F-33-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 6 2/2, 1969; F-33-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-2)
  - Official minutes Vol. 6a 1/2, 1969; F-33-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 6a 2/2, 1969; F-33-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 7 1/2, 1970; F-33-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 7 2/2, 1970; F-33-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 7a 1/2, 1970; F-33-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 7a 2/2, 1970; F-33-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 8 1/2, 1971; F-33-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 8 2/2, 1971; F-33-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-3)
  - Official minutes Vol. 8a, 1971; F-33-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 9 1/2, 1972; F-33-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 9 2/2, 1972; F-33-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 9a, 1972; F-33-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 10 1/2, 1973; F-33-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 10 2/2, 1973; F-33-1-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-4)
  - Official minutes Vol. 10a, 1973; F-33-1-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 11, 1974; F-33-1-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 12, 1975; F-33-1-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 13 1/2, 1976; F-33-1-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 13 2/2, 1976; F-33-1-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 14 1/2, 1977; F-33-1-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 14 2/2, 1977; F-33-1-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-5)
  - Official minutes Vol. 15 1/2, 1978; F-33-1-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
  - Official minutes Vol. 15 2/2, 1978; F-33-1-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
  - Official minutes Vol. 16, 1979; F-33-1-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
  - Official minutes Vol. 17, 1979; F-33-1-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
  - Official minutes Vol. 18 1/2, 1980; F-33-1-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
  - Official minutes Vol. 18 2/2, 1980; F-33-1-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-6)
- Agenda support papers, 1963 - 2003; F-33-2; 15.83 m of textual records
  These files were kept by the Secretary and Assistant to the Board of Governors and contain documents that provide background information for the various agenda items. In most cases, the documents formed part of packages that were sent to Board members, selected University officials, and campus organizations prior to each Board meeting. A few documents were kept by the Board secretary for her own reference and did not circulate. After 2003, agenda support papers were filed in docket packages alongside the meeting agendas and minutes. To view support papers from 2004 onwards, see series F-33-10 Meeting dockets.
  Series includes agendas, unsigned minutes, and support papers including correspondence; reports; financial statements; board committee minutes, contracts; architectural drawings; personnel records such as c.v.'s, reference letters and appointment forms; news clippings and other documents.
  Donna Laws was the Board Secretary from 1968 to 1993.
  - Agenda support papers (1st.). Oct. 1963, F-33-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers (2nd.). Nov. 1963, F-33-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers (3rd.). Dec. 1963, F-33-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1964, F-33-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. June 1964, F-33-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. July 1964, F-33-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Aug. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-7)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1964, F-33-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. Mar. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. May 1965, F-33-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. June 1965, F-33-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-8)
  - Agenda support papers. July 1965, F-33-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Aug. 5, 1965, F-33-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Aug. 26 1965, F-33-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1965, F-33-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-9)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 20, 1966, F-33-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 25, 1966, F-33-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Feb. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Feb. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Feb. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-10)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Mar. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Mar. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Mar. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers. Apr. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Apr. 27 and 29 1966, F-33-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. May 1966, F-33-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. May 1966, F-33-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-11)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. June 1966, F-33-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. June 1966, F-33-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers. July 1966, F-33-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Aug. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Aug. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 33-12)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Oct. 6, 1966, F-33-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Nov. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Nov. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1966, F-33-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 33-13)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 33-14)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 33-14)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 33-14)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 33-14)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Mar. 20, 1967, F-33-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 33-14)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 33-15)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 33-15)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 33-15)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. May 1967, F-33-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 33-15)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. May 1967, F-33-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 33-15)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1967, F-33-2-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1967, F-33-2-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1967, F-33-2-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). July 7, 1967, F-33-2-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Aug. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Aug. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Sept. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Sept. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 33-16)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Oct. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Oct. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Nov. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Nov. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Nov. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Dec. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Dec. 1967, F-33-2-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 33-17)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Jan. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Jan. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Jan. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Feb. 1, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 1/5. Mar. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 2/5. Mar. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 3/5. Mar. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 33-18)
  - Agenda support papers 4/5. Mar. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 5/5. Mar. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Apr. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Apr. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. May 1968, F-33-2-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. May 1968, F-33-2-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). May 31, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2 (special meetings). June 2 and 5, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2 (special meetings). June 2 and 5, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 33-19)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). July 16, 29, 31, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. July 1968, F-33-2-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. July 1968, F-33-2-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Aug. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Aug. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). Nov. 25, Dec. 5, 1968, F-33-2-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1968, F-33-2-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 33-20)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Jan. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Jan. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Feb. 6, 1969, F-33-2-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Feb. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Feb. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers 1/2. Mar. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers 2/2. Mar. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 33-21)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). Apr. 15, 1969, F-33-2-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. Apr. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. Apr. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. Apr. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). May 2, 1969, F-33-2-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. May 1969, F-33-2-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. May 1969, F-33-2-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. May 1969, F-33-2-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. June 1969, F-33-2-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 33-22)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. June 1969, F-33-2-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. June 1969, F-33-2-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers (special meeting). June 27, 1969, F-33-2-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers (special meetings). July 2, 13, 1969, F-33-2-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers 1/3. July 1969, F-33-2-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers 2/3. July 1969, F-33-2-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers 3/3. July 1969, F-33-2-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 33-23)
  - Agenda support papers. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 1/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 2/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 3/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 4/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 5/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 6/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 33-24)
  - Agenda support papers 7/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers 8/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers 9/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers 10/10. Aug. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers. Sept. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers. Oct. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 33-25)
  - Agenda support papers. Nov. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-141 (Archival box - standard 33-26)
  - Agenda support papers. Dec. 1969, F-33-2-0-0-142 (Archival box - standard 33-26)
  - Agenda support papers. Jan. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 33-26)
  - Agenda support papers. Feb. 1970, F-33-2-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 33-26)